All right. Here's my solution.
下面说说我的实现方法
I created a function that initializes the weights of
我创建了一个函数 它会使用
our model using values taken from a normal distribution.
从正态分布里取样的值初始化模型的权重
Again, just another function that we can apply to the module weights.
它是另一个可以应用到模块权重上的函数
Here, I'm defining a distribution with a mean of
在这里定义一个分布
zero and a standard deviation of one over square root n,
均值为 0 标准差为 1/√n￣
where n are the number of inputs to a given layer.
n 表示给定层级的输入数量
So, the range that these weights cover should change
因此这些权重所在的范围
based on the number of inputs to a linear layer,
应该根据线性层级的输入数量变化
and as usual, I have a bias of zero.
像往常一样 偏差的权重设为 0
Then, I'm creating two models to compare.
然后创建两个模型加以比较
The first, Model Uniform Rule.
首先是 model_uniform_rule
I'm initializing using our function from above, weights_init_uniform_rule.
使用上面的函数 weights_init_uniform_rule 初始化权重
Then, I'm creating another model that uses the function I
然后创建另一个模型
defined right here with weights from a normal distribution.
它使用在这里定义的函数 权重来自正态分布
For me, it's easiest to create new models right before I compare them.
对我来说 先创建新的模型 然后再比较模型 这样最简单
This way I know I haven't accidentally trained
因为这样我就能避免
one of them for a couple more epics and another one.
两个模型的训练轮数不一致的情况
After I've initialized my two models,
初始化两个模型后
I'm comparing them by creating a model list and using my compare_init_weights function.
通过创建模型列表并使用 compare_init_weights 函数比较这两个模型
Here we can see that the model initialized with weights from
此图显示了分别用正态分布和均匀分布
a normal distribution and from a uniform distribution, both behave similarly.
两个初始化权重的模型行为比较相似
Please note how low the starting loss value is here.
注意 这里的起始损失值很低
This similar behavior is likely because our network is so small.
两个模型相似的行为可能是因为网络很小
A larger neural network will pick more weight values from each of these distributions,
大型网络将从这两个分布中选择更多权重值
magnifying the effect of both initialization styles.
两种初始化方式的效果就会有更明显的区分
So, if the normal distribution shows a small improvement here,
如果正态分布表明有很小的改善
you can imagine that this could be magnified in a larger model.
那么可以想象对大型模型的改善会放大
I'd also like to point out really how far we've come.
我还要指出 我们取得了很大的成果
If we scroll up all the way to our constant weight values,
上拉页面 看看常量权重值
we can see that we've really improved.
可以看出模型改善了很多
We've gone from pretty bad constant weights to
最初是效果很差的常量权重
adding some randomness using a uniform distribution.
然后 我们使用均匀分布引入随机性
This allows our model to make more informative mistakes that it can better learn from.
使模型能犯更有启发性的错误
Finally, we went over the general rule for selecting weights from arrange,
最后我们了解了选择权重范围的一般法则
which depends on the number of inputs a layer sees.
该范围取决于层级看到的输入数量
Now, we've seen that selecting weights from a uniform or
现在可以看出 在训练过程中
a normal distribution can help us reach a high accuracy pretty quickly as we train.
从均匀分布或正态分布中选择权重有助于模型快速达到较高的准确率
Now, let's test out one more model and that's one
现在再测试一种模型
without any explicit way initialization.
这种模型没有明确的初始化方法
So, here, I'm simply instantiate in a model not
在这里直接实例化一个模型
passing anything and not applying any initial weights,
不传入任何参数并且不应用任何初始权重
I'm passing this model alone with a title into our comparison function.
将此模型和名称传入比较函数中
Now, you can actually see that the default behavior is quite good.
可以看到默认行为效果很不错
In fact, it looks really similar to our model
看起来和根据均匀分布
with initial weights taken from a uniform distribution,
初始化权重的模型行为很像
and this is because every type of pi torch layer has
这是因为每种 PyTorch 层级
a default weight initialization that happens behind the scenes.
在后台都有一种默认的权重初始化方式
In fact, we can see this default initialization by looking at the module source code.
我们可以通过查看模块源代码了解这种默认初始化方式
Here's the source code for a linear layer in Pi torch.
这是 PyTorch 中线性层级的源代码
Here in the reset parameters function,
在这个 reset_parameters 函数中可以看出
we can see that every linear layer is actually
每个线性层级的初始权重
initialized with weights taken from a uniform distribution.
都来自均匀分布
In fact, even the bias has some random range.
甚至偏差都具有随机范围
But I would caution you to be careful about this default initialization,
但是要注意这种默认初始化方式
it will often be the case that weights taken from something like
通常根据正态分布初始化权重
a normal distribution instead can get us better results.
能够获得更好的结果
So, it may still be useful especially if you're trying to train
因此正态分布依然很有用
the best models to initialize the weights of
尤其当你尝试训练最佳模型
a model according to the rules that you define,
并根据你定义的规则初始化模型权重的时候
and this is not the end of your learning path here.
学习之路并不是到此就结束了
You're encouraged to look at the different types of
建议你查看各种不同类型的
common initialization distributions in the documentation.
初始化分布文档
As you continue to learn in the classroom,
当你继续在此课堂里学习教程时
you'll also see more resources for learning about and practicing weight initialization.
我们会提供更多关于学习和练习权重初始化的资源